const a="We could not find what you asked for, but got you this",e="irk",o=200,i=30,t=[{id:15,question:"Literally, Boko Haram means  ",option:{a:"book is forbidden  ",b:"education is forbidden  ",c:"Western education is forbidden  ",d:"school is forbidden  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:13,question:"The first place of Muslims ig atio   as ___",option:{a:"Abyssinia  ",b:"Taif  ",c:"Medina  ",d:"Yathrib "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:18,question:"Ibadah refers to  ",option:{a:"worship of ancestors  ",b:"worship of the Prophet  ",c:"worship of the caliphs ",d:"worship of Allah  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:30,question:"The reason Q.  2: 219 forbids wine ad gambling is because  ",option:{a:"they lead one to greater sin than gain  ",b:"they lead to poverty ultimately ",c:"they lead to extravagance and intoxication  ",d:"they make a Muslim to abandon religion  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:20,question:"Which one of the following is not associated with shirk _____ ",option:{a:"idol worship  ",b:"trinity  ",c:"monotheism  ",d:"henotheism "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:1,question:"The reason Mecca suwar lay emphasis on oneness of Allah is because  ",option:{a:"it was the only way to call Mecca to Islam  ",b:"it is the only article of faith  ",c:"it is the only article of peace between Prophet Muhammad and the Mecca  ",d:"the pre-Islamic Mecca were idolatrous "},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:29,question:"The prophet admonishes that if an abomination is found, a true Muslim should at least  ",option:{a:"hate if from his heart  ",b:"change it with his hands immediately  ",c:"condemn it publicly  ",d:"declare Jihad  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:19,question:"Shirk means ____  ",option:{a:"monotheism ",b:"polytheism",c:"henotheism  ",d:"syncretism "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:26,question:"Talaq al-",option:{a:"irrevocable ",b:"revocable  ",c:"impermissible  ",d:"detestable "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:8,question:"One importance of wearing the Ihram during Hajj is_____  ",option:{a:"it directs the mind of all Muslims towards Allah  ",b:"it purifies the Muslims  ",c:"it makes all Muslims equal  ",d:"it distinguishes pilgrims by country of origin  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:17,question:"If Alhaji Musa Ayuba invested N10, 000: 00 in a business and made a profit of N2, 000: 00 at the",option:{a:"N215.00",b:"N100: 00  ",c:"N50:00  ",d:"N1000:00 "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:5,question:"Suratul-Kawthar was revealed following the _____ of the Mecca  ",option:{a:"uproar  ",b:"insinuation  ",c:"intolerance  ",d:"resistance  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:14,question:"Al-Tawrat was revealed to  ",option:{a:"Isa  ",b:"Musa  ",c:"Prophet Muhammad  ",d:"Idris "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:2,question:"Uthman B. Affan reigned between  ",option:{a:"644 and 656 ",b:"657 and 688  ",c:"655 and 657  ",d:"644 and 655  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:23,question:"According to Islamic traditions, inability to marriage may rise as a consequence of   ",option:{a:"defects in sex organs  ",b:"permanent illness  ",c:"impotence  ",d:"all of the above  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"d",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:10,question:"The oa d gi e  to P ophet Muhad is the first  e elatio  of the Qu a  tells us about ____ ",option:{a:"education  ",b:"prosperity  ",c:"worship  ",d:"Allah "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:6,question:"Zakat is paid on the following except____  ",option:{a:"cash  ",b:"cattle  ",c:"slaves",d:"all of the above "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:25,question:"The main message of ayay Amanar-Rasul is  ",option:{a:"the significance of knowledge  ",b:"the articles of faith  ",c:"the pillars of Islam  ",d:"payment of Zakat "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:22,question:"Lakum dinukum wa Liya dinin means  ",option:{a:"religion is good  ",b:"to you is my religion and to me yours  ",c:"to you is your religion and to me is my religion ",d:"my religion is better than yours  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:7,question:"The i itial suggestio  to o pile the Qu a   as aised   ",option:{a:"A u Bak  ",b:"Umar B. Khattab  ",c:"Zaid B. Thabit  ",d:"Uthman B. Affan  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:12,question:"The spokesman of the Muslims before Emperor Negus was ",option:{a:"Jaafar  ",b:"Al-As  ",c:"Abu Musa  ",d:"Masa Musa  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:11,question:"?eek k o ledge, e e  u to Chi a   ea s ____ ",option:{a:"go to China to seek knowledge  ",b:"knowledge is found in China  ",c:"go at any length to seek knowledge  ",d:"knowledge must be sought in china   "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:28,question:"When Prophet Muhammad got to Yathrib, he had to first and foremost settle the feud between  ",option:{a:"Aws and Khazraj  ",b:"banu Nadir and Mecca  ",c:"Mecca and Medina ",d:"Aws and Nadir  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:9,question:"The reason for the declaration of Jihad against the Islamic state of Borno by Muhammad Bello wasbecause of the people",option:{a:"rebellion  ",b:"extremism ",c:"syncretism  ",d:"fundamentalism "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:27,question:"The word Hafizi in Q.  82: 10 means  ",option:{a:"angels  ",b:"jinns  ",c:"spirits ",d:"man  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:4,question:"Hajjatul Wada of Prophet Muhammad was delivered in ",option:{a:"632",b:"630",c:"628",d:"631"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:21,question:"If a Muslim prays five times daily on a regular basis, how many times will he have prayed a regular ",option:{a:"1825",b:"1835",c:"1835",d:"1845"},section:"",image:"",answer:"a",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:24,question:"Walam yakun lahu Kufuwan Ahadun is_____  ",option:{a:"the second ayat of the 112th surah  ",b:"sixth ayat of the 111th surah  ",c:"fourth ayat of the 112th surah ",d:"seventh ayat of the 114th surah  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:3,question:"The final and total prohibition of intoxicants is contained in Surah  ",option:{a:"al-Baqarah  ",b:"an-Nisa  ",c:"al-Maidah  ",d:"al- I a  "},section:"",image:"",answer:"c",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"},{id:16,question:"Wudu means  ",option:{a:"ablution",b:"dry ablution  ",c:"water ablution  ",d:"wet ablution "},section:"",image:"",answer:"b",solution:"",examtype:"post-utme-aaua",examyear:"2012"}],s={message:a,subject:e,status:200,total:30,data:t};export{t as data,s as default,a as message,o as status,e as subject,i as total};
